Are you ready, kids?
孩子们，你们准备好了吗？
KIDS:
Aye, aye, Captain!
儿童：
是啊是啊，队长！
I can't hear you.
我听不到你说话。
[ louder]:
Aye, aye, Captain!
[更大声]：
是啊是啊，队长！
♪ Oh... ♪
♪ 哦...♪
♪ Who lives in a pineapple
under the sea? ♪
♪ 谁住在菠萝里
在海底？ ♪
♪ SpongeBob SquarePants!♪
♪ 海绵宝宝！♪
♪ Absorbent and yellow
and porous is he. ♪
♪ 吸水性和黄色
他是多孔的。 ♪
♪ SpongeBob SquarePants!♪
♪ 海绵宝宝！♪
♪ If nautical nonsense be
something you wish... ♪
♪ 如果航海方面的废话是
你想要的东西...♪
♪ SpongeBob SquarePants!♪
♪ 海绵宝宝！♪
♪ Then drop on the deck
and flop like a fish. ♪
♪ 然后落在甲板上
然后像鱼一样扑通扑通。 ♪
♪ SpongeBob SquarePants!♪
♪ 海绵宝宝！♪
♪ Ready?
SpongeBob SquarePants! ♪
♪ 准备好了吗？
海绵宝宝！ ♪
♪ SpongeBob SquarePants! ♪
♪ 海绵宝宝！ ♪
[ laughs heartily]
[开怀大笑]
[ plays airy tune]
[演奏轻快的曲子]
Captioning sponsored
by MTV NETWORKS
字幕赞助
由 MTV 网络提供
[ banging on door]
[敲门]
Mr. Krabs, some guy in a suit
wants to come in before we open.
蟹老板，一个穿西装的家伙
想在我们开门之前进来。
What? Guy in a suit?
什么？穿西装的家伙？
No! It's a tax collector!
不！原来是个税吏啊！
Hide us, SpongeBob!
隐藏我们，海绵宝宝！
KRABS [ muffled]:
Now we'll walk nonchalantly
to the rear exit.
螃蟹[闷闷不乐]：
现在我们要漫不经心地走
到后出口。
He's got a card.
他有一张卡。
"R.A. PennyPincher
Vending Supplies."
“R.A.彭尼平彻
自动售货用品。”
KRABS:
What?!
螃蟹：
什么？！
My machine has arrived?!
我的机器到了？！
Ooh, let him in,
let him in, let him in!
哦，让他进来，
让他进来，让他进来！
Bring it in, boys.
把它带进来，孩子们。
That's it, set her down easy.
就这样，轻松地把她放下来。
Here are the keys,
Mr. Krabs.
这是钥匙，
蟹老板。
Happy vending!
快乐售卖！
What is it?
它是什么？
Only the greatest
moneymaker
只有最伟大的
摇钱树
since the Krabby Patty.
自从蟹黄饼开始。
Gentlemen, meet
"Skill Crane"!
先生们，见面吧
“技能鹤”！
[ dazed]:
Ooh... Skill Crane.
[茫然]：
哦...技能鹤。
At a quarter a pop,
在四分之一的流行声中，
this thing will pay for itself
in no time.
这件事会收回成本
很快。
Which reminds me--
step up, boys.
这让我想起——
站起来，孩子们。
First one's free.
第一个是免费的。
Thanks, Mr. Krabs.
谢谢，蟹老板。
No, thanks, I'll pass.
不，谢谢，我会过去的。
Come on, Squidward,
you know you want to.
来吧，章鱼哥，
你知道你想要。
[ sighing]:
Okay.
[叹气]：
好的。
If you insist.
如果你坚持的话。
Thanks.
谢谢。
Squidward!
章鱼哥！
In the machine!
在机器里！
All right, all right.
好吧，好吧。
[ in bored monotone]:
Oh, boy, what fun.
[无聊单调]：
哦，孩子，多有趣啊。
SKILL CRANE:
You lose!
技能起重机：
你输了！
Did you see that, SpongeBob?!
你看到了吗，海绵宝宝？！
I almost got that
on my first try!
我几乎明白了
我第一次尝试！
My work here is done.
我这里的工作已经完成了。
They don't call me
他们不打电话给我
"Squidward Manual-
Dexterity-Tentacles"
for nothing.
《章鱼哥手册》——
敏捷-触手”
无缘无故。
[ soft crackling]
[轻柔的噼啪声]
Well, why don't
I give it a try?
好吧，为什么不呢
我试试？
[ laughing]
[笑]
Good luck. You'll never...
祝你好运。你永远不会...
SKILL CRANE:
Winner!
技能起重机：
获胜者！
[ siren whoops]
[警笛呼喊]
It's a bear!
这是一只熊！
I'm going to call you Barry.
我要叫你巴里。
Hmm-- beginner's luck.
嗯——初学者的运气。
Now it's the master's turn.
现在轮到主人了。
[ crane whirring]
[起重机呼呼]
[ buzzer sounds]
[蜂鸣器响]
SKILL CRANE:
Loser!
技能起重机：
失败者！
Wow, Squidward,
you flipped
him over!
哇，章鱼哥，
你翻转了
他完了！
That takes an awful
amount of skill.
这需要一个可怕的
技能量。
Well, thank you for saying so.
嗯，谢谢你这么说。
Barry says
he's getting lonely.
巴里说
他越来越孤独了。
Don't worry, Barry,
别担心，巴里，
I'll get you a friend.
我会给你找个朋友。
Ha! If you think
哈!如果你认为
you're going to win again...
你会再次获胜...
SKILL CRANE:
Winner!
技能起重机：
获胜者！
[ siren whoops]
[警笛呼喊]
There you go, Barry!
给你，巴里！
Oh, I loosened
that one up for you.
哦，我松了
那是给你的。
You would have never won
that without myskill.
你永远不会赢
那没有我的技巧。
Wow, thanks for your help,
Squidward.
哇，谢谢你的帮助，
章鱼哥。
Hmm.
唔。
I bet I win at this thing
the very next time I try.
我打赌我在这件事上赢了
下次我尝试时。
Now, all I've got to do is...
现在，我所要做的就是……
At a quarter a pop,
在四分之一的流行声中，
this thing pays for itself
in no time.
这件事是值得的
很快。
Ha! I'm not falling
for that malarkey.
哈!我没有坠落
为了那个胡言乱语。
[ quarters falling
into machine]
[季度下降
入机]
[ bell dinging, siren whooping]
[铃声响起，警笛鸣响]
Hey, Squidward.
嘿，章鱼哥。
[ quarters falling into machine;
Squidward groans]
[ 硬币掉进机器里；
章鱼哥呻吟]
Hey, Squidward.
嘿，章鱼哥。
[ quarters falling into machine;
Squidward groans]
[ 硬币掉进机器里；
章鱼哥呻吟]
[ bell dinging]
[铃声响起]
Hey, Squidward.
嘿，章鱼哥。
[ SpongeBob laughing]
[海绵宝宝大笑]
SPONGEBOB:
Okay, Mrs. Wiggles--
海绵宝宝：
好吧，维格斯夫人——
order up!
订购吧！
Barry cooked this one
all by himself!
巴里煮了这个
全靠他自己！
Oh, he makes me
so proud.
哦，他让我
很自豪。
[ eerie, creaky voice]:
Squid-ward?
[怪异、嘎吱作响的声音]：
鱿鱼区？
[ hook squeaking softly]
[钩子轻轻吱吱作响]
[ eerie, creaky voice]:
Squid-ward?
[怪异、嘎吱作响的声音]：
鱿鱼区？
Oh, what the...?
哦，那是什么……？
All right,
let's get this over with.
好吧，
让我们结束这件事吧。
Need change?
需要改变吗？
There you are.
你就在那里。
Gee, thanks.
哎呀，谢谢。
No, no, Mr. Squidward.
不，不，章鱼哥先生。
Thank you.
谢谢。
[ crane whirring]
[起重机呼呼]
SKILL CRANE:
You lose!
技能起重机：
你输了！
Need some more change?
需要更多改变吗？
[ buzzer droning]
[蜂鸣器嗡嗡声]
[ beeping]
[嘟嘟声]
[ buzzer droning]
[蜂鸣器嗡嗡声]
[ mechanical voice laughing]
[机械笑声]
[ change jingling]
【变叮当】
[ buzzer droning]
[蜂鸣器嗡嗡声]
SKILL CRANE:
You lose!
技能起重机：
你输了！
Need some change?
需要一些改变吗？
No.
不。
W-Why?
W-为什么？
[ softly]:
Because I'm all out of...
[轻声]：
因为我已经没力气了...
money!
钱！
All out of...
全部出于...
Hmm.
唔。
Boys, it's payday!
孩子们，发薪日到了！
[ gasps]
[喘气]
But Mr. Krabs,
today is Monday.
但是蟹老板先生，
今天是星期一。
Uh... no, it's payday,
me boy.
呃...不，今天是发薪日，
我男孩。
Here's your check,
SpongeBob.
这是你的支票，
海绵宝宝。
♪ Money, money, money,
money, money! ♪
♪ 钱，钱，钱，
钱，钱！ ♪
I took the liberty
我冒昧地
of turning your paycheck
into quarters
改变你的薪水
分成四等分
just in case you want to,
oh, I don't know,
以防万一你愿意
哦，我不知道，
do laundry or buy a soda
洗衣服或买苏打水
or... something.[ change jingling]
或者...什么东西。[改变叮当声]
Very funny, Mr. Krabs!
非常有趣，蟹老板！
If I can't win
如果我赢不了
one of those stupid things
with thisquarter,
那些愚蠢的事情之一
与本季度相比，
I'm walking away.
我要走开。
Pardon me, Squidward,
SpongeBear Junior here
请原谅我，章鱼哥，
小海绵熊在这里
wants me to win him
a little brother.
希望我赢得他
一个小兄弟。
SKILL CRANE:
You are a winner!
技能起重机：
你是赢家！
Huh?
啊？
Two in one quarter?
一季度两个？
That's not fair.
这不公平。
What's that, Clown Frown?
那是什么，小丑皱眉？
[ horn tootling]
[ 喇叭声 ]
Oh, you'd rather sit
next to Lovely Lion?
哦，你宁愿坐
可爱的狮子旁边？
[ crane whirring]
[起重机呼呼]
There you are, nice and cozy.
你就在那里，美好又舒适。
See you later, Squidward.
稍后见，章鱼哥。
[ Squidward sighs]
[章鱼哥叹气]
A little mind-numbing television
有点让人麻木的电视
ought to help me forget
about that stupid machine.
应该帮助我忘记
关于那台愚蠢的机器。
[ mechanical laughter,
buzzer from crane droning]
[机械笑声，
起重机嗡嗡声的蜂鸣器]
[ screams]
[尖叫声]
You've had a rough day, Squiddy,
你这一天过得很艰难，鱿鱼，
but that doesn't mean tomorrow
won't be better.
但这并不意味着明天
不会更好。
[ mechanical laughter,
buzzer from crane droning]
[机械笑声，
起重机嗡嗡声的蜂鸣器]
Oh... phooey!
哦...呸！
[ whimpers]
[呜咽]
[ teeth chattering]
[牙齿打战]
Oh!
哦！
[ crane whirring]
[起重机呼呼]
[ buzzer drones]
[蜂鸣器无人机]
I got to win that crane!
我一定要赢得那只起重机！
[ yelps]
[尖叫声]
Just once!
就一次！
Please, oh, please,
let me win one time.
拜托，噢，拜托，
让我赢一次。
Squid, I think
you have a problem.
我觉得是鱿鱼
你有问题。
No, he doesn't!
不，他不！
You don't listen to him,
Squidward,
你不听他的话
章鱼哥，
you keep playing
until you win!
你继续玩
直到你赢！
What's this?
这是什么？
The deed to my house.
我家的地契。
Okey-dokey, then.
那么好吧。
Carry on.
继续。
[ sobbing]
[抽泣]
If I could just win once,
I'd never play again!
如果我能赢一次就好了
我再也不会玩了！
[ sobbing]
[抽泣]
Hey-- you want me
to tell you the secret
嘿——你想要我
告诉你这个秘密
of how to win
on this machine?
论如何获胜
在这台机器上？
SpongeBob--
there's a secret?
海绵宝宝——
有秘密吗？
Mm-hmm.
嗯嗯。
Tell me... the... secret.
告诉我……秘密。
Are you ready to be a winner?
您准备好成为赢家了吗？
Yes!
Yeah?
是的！
是的？
Yes?
Yeah!
是的？
是的！
Yeah!
Yes?
是的！
是的？
SpongeBob, the secret!
海绵宝宝，秘密！
Okay, Squidward, okay!
好吧，章鱼哥，好吧！
I face the crane,
deposit my quarter...
我面对着起重机，
存入我的四分之一...
then I close my eyes.
然后我闭上眼睛。
Close your eyes?
闭上眼睛吗？
Quiet, Squidward--
I'm being the crane.
安静，章鱼哥——
我就是那只起重机
Oh, that's ludi...
噢，那是路迪……
SKILL CRANE:
Winner!
技能起重机：
获胜者！
See? Now you try.
看？现在你试试。
This is ridiculous.
这太荒谬了。
If I close my eyes,
how will I know
where...
如果我闭上眼睛
我怎么知道
哪里...
Do you want to win or not?
你想赢还是不想赢？
Yes! Yes, I do!
是的！是的，我愿意！
Okay.
好的。
Squidward,
put your quarter in.
章鱼哥，
把你的25美分硬币放进去。
But this is
my last quarter.
但这是
我的最后一个季度。
In the machine, Squidward.
在机器里，章鱼哥。
Okay, okay!
好吧好吧！
Close your eyes.
闭上你的眼睛。
Now be the crane.
现在成为起重机。
Be the crane.
成为起重机。
SPONGEBOB:
Be the crane.
海绵宝宝：
成为起重机。
Be the crane.
SKILL CRANE:
Winner!
技能起重机：
获胜者！
[ bell dings]
[铃声]
[ whooping]
[呼喊]
Yeah!
是的！
I knew I could do it!
我知道我能做到！
[ laughing]
[笑]
I'm a winner!
我是赢家！
You're a winner!
你是赢家！
I am a winner, aren't I?
我是胜利者，不是吗？
Winner, winner, winner!
赢家，赢家，赢家！
Winner...!
优胜者...！
I'm a winner, everybody!
大家好，我是胜利者！
You hear that?!
你听到了吗？
[ cricket chirping]
[蟋蟀鸣叫]
[ door crashes open]
[门突然打开了]
I'm... a winner.
我是……胜利者。
Funny, last time I checked,
you were a cashier.
有趣的是，我上次检查时，
你是一名收银员。
Yuck it up all you want,
Mr. Krabs, but just remember:
随心所欲地吐出来吧
螃蟹先生，但请记住：
You're yucking
in the presence of a winner!
你在呕吐
在胜利者面前！
Ha!
哈!
I'll try to remember that.
我会尽力记住这一点。
3,498 of Squidward's quarters,
3,499 of Squidward's quarters...
章鱼哥的3,498个宿舍，
章鱼哥的 3,499 个宿舍……
Triple-decker on deck.
甲板上有三层甲板。
Make way for the winner!
为胜利者让路！
SKILL CRANE:
You lose!
技能起重机：
你输了！
[ sighs]
[叹气]
[ softly]:
You didn't win
the prize?
[轻声]：
你没有赢
奖品？
No.
不。
You know what
that means?
你知道吗
这意味着？
No. What?
不，什么？
It means...
这意味着...
you have no skills
and you're a loser!
你没有技能
你是个失败者！
Ha!
哈!
[ cackling]
[咯咯笑]
I'm a winner,
see my prize.
我是胜利者，
看看我的奖品。
You're a loser
who sits and cries.
你是个失败者
谁坐着哭泣。
[ cackling]
[咯咯笑]
Ow, ow, ow, ow,
ow, ow, ow, ow!
噢，噢，噢，噢，
噢，噢，噢，噢！
Did you see how
I handled that crane?
你看到了吗
我操控了那台起重机？
I sure did.
我确实做到了。
I think I have
the magic touch.
我想我有
神奇的触感。
Uh-huh.
嗯嗯。
I just closed my eyes
我刚刚闭上眼睛
and became the crane.
并变成了起重机。
[ bored]:
Oh, yeah,
you're the man.
[无聊]：
哦，是的，
你就是那个男人。
SpongeBob, look.
海绵宝宝，看。
Uh, Squidward, I don't think
the same principles apply.
呃，章鱼哥，我不认为
同样的原则也适用。
Be the crane.
成为起重机。
Wait, Squidward!
等等，章鱼哥！
Be the crane.
成为起重机。
He did it!
他做到了！
Yay, Squidward!
耶，章鱼哥！
Be the crane, be the crane.
成为起重机，成为起重机。
Be the crane...
成为起重机...
You know this guy?
你认识这个人吗？
Yeah,
that's Squidward.
是的，
那是章鱼哥。
He's got
the magic touch.
他有
神奇的触感。
Ding!
叮！
Ta-dah!
哒哒！
[ screams]
[尖叫声]
Squidward,
open your eyes!
章鱼哥，
睁开你的眼睛！
Oh, uh... be the crane,
be the crane.
哦，呃...成为起重机，
是起重机。
Look out, SpongeBob,
I can't stop!
小心，海绵宝宝，
我停不下来！
Be the crane,
be the crane!
成为起重机，
成为起重机！
Okay, don't be the crane,
don't be the crane!
好吧，别当起重机，
不要成为起重机！
[ Squidward screaming]
[章鱼哥尖叫]
[ all screaming]
[全都尖叫]
[ crashing]
[崩溃]
What the...?!
什么……？！
Oh, my, oh, my.
哦，天哪，哦，天哪。
Time to go, Teddy.
是时候出发了，泰迪。
Just where do you think
you're going, crane master?
只是你觉得哪里
鹤大师，你要去吗？
You ain't going anywhere.
你哪儿也不去。
[ whistling; crane chugging]
[ 吹口哨；起重机嘎嘎作响]
SPONGEBOB:
Hang on, buddy!
海绵宝宝：
坚持住，伙计！
I got you!
我接到你了！
I guess I can only pick up toys.
我想我只能捡起玩具。
[ workers growling]
[工人咆哮]
Uh-oh.
呃哦。
[ snoring and wheezing]
[打鼾和喘息]
[ snoring and humming]
[打鼾和嗡嗡声]
[ snoring and muttering]
[打鼾和咕哝]
[ foghorn blowing]
[雾号吹响]
SpongeBob.
海绵宝宝。
Good morning,
Squidward!
早上好，
章鱼哥！
SpongeBob, what are
you doing in my house?
海绵宝宝，什么是
你在我家做什么？
I came to make sure
you don't oversleep
and miss work.
我来是为了确认一下
你没有睡过头
并错过工作。
Oh, gee, SpongeBob,
哦，天啊，海绵宝宝，
that's very thoughtful
of you.
这很周到
你的。
My pleasure, Squidward.
我很荣幸，章鱼哥。
That's what good
neighbors are for.
就是这样好
邻居是为了。
You did overlook one
teensy, little detail, however.
你确实忽略了一个
然而，很小，细节很少。
What's that, Squidward?
那是什么，章鱼哥？
It's Sunday!
今天是星期日！
A good neighbor doesn't
bother me on Sunday!
好邻居不会
周日烦我！
Sunday!
星期日！
No wonder Squidward's grumpy.
难怪章鱼哥脾气暴躁。
He forgot his Sunday papers.
他忘记了周日报纸。
This will show Squidward
I'm a good neighbor.
这将显示章鱼哥
我是个好邻居。
I'll bring it to him.
我会把它带给他。
[ grunting]
[咕噜声]
Man, this is heavy!
伙计，这很重！
Oh! Pardon me.
哦！对不起。
Hey, watch where
you're going!
嘿，看哪里
你走吧！
[ screams]
[尖叫声]
A newspaper monster!
报纸怪物！
[ screams]:
Aah, monster!
[尖叫声]：
啊啊，怪物！
[ screaming]
[尖叫]
Will you two nincompoops
kindly quiet down?!
你们两个笨蛋愿意吗
请安静一点？！
I am not going to let them ruin
the rest of my Sunday.
我不会让他们毁掉
我周日剩下的时间。
[ humming]
[嗡嗡声]
My Sunday relaxation kit.
我的周日放松套装。
Let's see, pillow, placed just
so for slight foot elevation...
让我们看看，枕头，刚刚放好
所以对于轻微的脚抬高...
flower to brighten the room...
鲜花可以照亮房间...
flower fragrance...
花香...
[ sighs]
[叹气]
And the final touch...
还有最后的接触...
[ touch tones beeping]
[ 按键音蜂鸣声 ]
Yes, I'd like to order
the Sunday special.
是的，我想订购
周日特别节目。
Yes, the pedicure-
and-foot-massage house call,
是的，修脚——
足部按摩上门服务，
that is correct.
这是正确的。
See you at 4:00, my good man.
4:00 见，我的好人。
This is going to be
a heavenly day.
这将是
天堂般的一天。
Oh, I almost forgot.
哦，我差点忘了。
Bon-bon.
邦邦。
Hello there,
heaven's little wonder.
你好，
天上的小奇迹。
Take me on a chocolate vacation.
带我去享受巧克力假期。
[ Patrick and SpongeBob
whoop like sirens]
[帕特里克和海绵宝宝
像警报一样呼喊]
Om...
嗡...
BOTH:
By the all-seeing eye,
两者：
以全视之眼来看，
ye are worthy,
we are not.
你们是值得的，
我们不是。
What are you
two idiots doing?
你是什么
两个白痴在做什么？
Secret ritual.
秘密仪式。
To inaugurate you
as president.
为您揭幕
作为总统。
Me? President of Bikini Bottom?
我？比基尼泳裤总裁？
I knew the people would come
to their senses.
我知道人们会来
到他们的感觉。
No, silly--
不，傻瓜——
not the president
of Bikini Bottom.
不是总统
的比基尼底部。
Even better.
甚至更好。
Better?
更好的？
You're the president
你是总统
of the Secret Royal Order
of the Good Neighbor Lodge.
秘密皇家勋章
好邻居旅馆的。
The what?
什么？
Is this some
stupid club
you two made up?
这是一些
愚蠢的俱乐部
你们两个和好了吗？
Oh!
哦！
[ both giggle]
[两人都咯咯笑]
Maybe.
或许。
[ both giggle]
[两人都咯咯笑]
It's a secret.
这是一个秘密。
[ both laugh]
[两人都笑了]
Fine!
美好的！
As my first presidential
decree, uh...
作为我的第一任总统
法令，呃……
why don't you, uh,
你为什么不，呃，
go out and paint
all the leaves
on the trees
出去画画
所有的叶子
在树上
to make the neighborhood
look nicer.
使邻里
看起来更好一些。
Now, out, out,
out, out, out.
现在，出去，出去，
出去，出去，出去。
That'll keep 'em busy
for a few Sundays.
这会让他们很忙
几个星期天。
What color should we
paint the leaves?
我们应该选择什么颜色
画叶子？
Aah! Polka dots.
啊啊！波尔卡圆点。
Now, don't
bother me anymore.
现在，不要
不再打扰我了。
BOTH:
Wow, polka dots!
两者：
哇，圆点！
Our new president
is a genius.
我们的新任总统
是个天才。
Yeah.
是的。
[ both laugh]
[两人都笑了]
BOTH:
See you later, Squidward.
两者：
稍后见，章鱼哥。
Whenever you're
ready, Patrick.
每当你在
准备好了，帕特里克。
Hold still, buddy.
别动，伙计。
Okay, Pat, give me
a quick shake.
好的，帕特，给我
快速摇晃。
Okey-dokey.
好吧，好吧。
Okay, I'm ready!
好的，我准备好了！
Hey, that worked
perfectly.
嘿，这有效
完美。
Come on,
good neighbor Patrick.
来吧，
好邻居帕特里克。
Let's paint
the town polka-dot.
我们来画画吧
小镇圆点。
[ clock chiming]
[时钟鸣响]
Oh, no, it's already noon.
哦，不对，已经是中午了。
I will be darned
if I let those morons
我会被诅咒的
如果我让那些白痴
eat up any more
of my valuable Sunday.
再吃下去
我宝贵的周日。
SPONGEBOB AND PATRICK:
♪ Good neighbors are we. ♪
海绵宝宝和帕特里克：
♪ 我们是好邻居。 ♪
♪ La-la-la-la-la. ♪
♪ 啦啦啦啦啦。 ♪
What's going on
out there?
发生了什么事
在那里？
Hi, President Squidward.
你好，章鱼哥总统。
Almost done painting...
快画完了...
[ screams]
My eyes!
[尖叫声]
我的眼睛！
[ screaming]
[尖叫]
Look out!
当心！
[ shrieks]
[尖叫声]
[ brakes screech]
[刹车声]
Oh, your poor man.
哦，你可怜的人。
You must be very sick.
你一定病得很重。
Let us take you
to the hospital.
让我们带你
去医院。
No, really,
I'm fine,
please.
不，真的，
我很好，
请。
No. I'm fine.
不，我很好。
[ tires screech]
[轮胎的尖叫声]
BOTH:
See you later, neighbor.
两者：
再见，邻居。
It isa lovely day
这是美好的一天
for a ride
in the country.
搭便车
在国内。
Yeah. Our president
sure knows how to live.
是的。我们的总裁
肯定知道如何生活。
I would like
to call this meeting
我想要
召开这次会议
of the Good Neighbor Lodge
to order.
好邻居旅馆的
订购。
Let's begin with roll call.
让我们从点名开始。
Patrick.
帕特里克.
[ snoring]
[打鼾]
Okay.
好的。
Squidward?
章鱼哥？
Squidward, you home?
章鱼哥，你在家吗？
Did you find him,
SpongeBob?
你找到他了吗，
海绵宝宝？
Nope. I guess
he's still on
his Sunday drive.
没有。我猜
他还在
他周日开车。
Or maybe he's on
a secret mission.
或者也许他正在
一项秘密任务。
I hope he's not
in danger.
我希望他不是
处于危险之中。
Danger?!
危险？！
As members of the
Good Neighbor Lodge,
作为成员
好邻居旅馆，
we are sworn to protect
our presidentefrom danger.
我们发誓要保护
我们的总统免遭危险。
Excuse me.
打扰一下。
Somebody ordered a relaxing
pedicure and foot massage:
有人点了一份放松的
修脚和足部按摩：
the Sunday special.
周日特别节目。
We better check
this guy out,
我们最好检查一下
这家伙出来了
make sure he's safe
for Squidward.
确保他安全
为了章鱼哥。
At least I still have my Sunday
pedicure to look forward to.
至少我还有周日
足疗值得期待。
[ SpongeBob and Patrick
giggling]
[海绵宝宝和帕特里克
咯咯笑]
What are you two
doing in my house?
你们两个是什么
在我家做什么？
We're checking
to make sure
我们正在检查
以确保
this guy really
is a certified
foot masseur
这家伙真的
是经过认证的
足部按摩师
and not some kind
of assassin.
而不是某种
的刺客。
Well, I say
he checks out a-okay.
好吧，我说
他检查了一下，好吧。
Squidward, have
you ever seen more
lovely French tips?
章鱼哥，有
你见过更多
可爱的法语小贴士？
French tips,
huh?
法语小贴士，
嗯？
All right, pal, make with a
relaxing foot massage, pronto!
好吧，朋友，用一个
放松足部按摩，很快！
Uh-oh. Uh, sorry,
your hour's up.
呃哦。呃，抱歉，
你的时间到了。
All right, you two, out!
好了，你们两个，出去吧！
Don't even think about dragging
your empty skulls around here
根本就别想拖
你的头骨空空如也
for the rest of the day
当天剩下的时间
or tomorrow
or next week!
或明天
或者下周！
Does that include...
这其中是否包括...
Yes, it does!
是的，确实如此！
Gee, Patrick,
do you think
哎呀，帕特里克，
你认为
Squidward was trying
to tell us something?
章鱼哥正在尝试
告诉我们一些事情？
Yes, I was!
是的，我是！
Youcall yourselves
good neighbors?
你们自称
好邻居？
You're the worst
neighbors ever!
你是最糟糕的
永远的邻居！
You don't deserve
to wear those fezzes!
你不值得
戴那些毡帽！
Gee, Pat, maybe
President Squidward's right.
哎呀，帕特，也许吧
章鱼哥总统是对的。
Yeah.
是的。
I guess we aren't good
neighbors after all.
我想我们都不好
毕竟是邻居。
No, you aren't!
不，你不是！
You're horrible neighbors!
你们真是可怕的邻居！
[ hyperventilates]
[换气过度]
And stop calling me
president!
别再打电话给我了
总统！
Come on, let's go.
来吧，我们走吧。
There are only three hours
of my Sunday left.
只有三个小时
我的周日离开了。
They took it all away.
他们把一切都拿走了。
I didn't even get to read
the Sunday paper.
我什至都没来得及读书
星期日报纸。
[ snarling]
[咆哮]
Good neighbors, my right...
好邻居，我的权利...
Hello.
你好。
[ reading aloud]:
[朗读]：
[ snickering maliciously]
[恶意窃笑]
[ laughing maniacally]
[疯狂大笑]
COMPUTER:
System activated.
电脑：
系统激活。
Well, that
ought to do it.
嗯，那个
应该这样做。
Let's see those imbeciles
try to get in here now.
让我们看看那些无知的人
现在尝试进入这里。
President Squidward?[ yelps]
章鱼哥总统？[尖叫]
What the...!
什么啊……！
We hereby present you
with this delicious cake.
我们在此向您介绍
有了这个美味的蛋糕。
SQUIDWARD [ reading]:
章鱼哥[阅读]：
Security system,
help!
安全系统，
帮忙！
Intruder alert,
intruder alert.
入侵者警报，
入侵者警报。
What's the matter
with you?
怎么了
和你在一起吗？
Oh, you infernal
contraption.
噢，你这个地狱般的人
装置。
I'll ship you off
to the scrap heap!
我会把你送走
到废品堆去！
[ shrieks]
[尖叫声]
[ zapping]
[ 电击 ]
What's going on?
这是怎么回事？
[ laughs]
[笑]
It's like
a carnival ride.
就像
嘉年华之旅。
Run for your lives!
为你的生命而奔跑！
[ Squidward shouts]
[章鱼哥大喊]
What the...
什么...
What are you doing?!
你在干什么？！
Huh?
啊？
I only have half an hour
of me-time left
我只有半个小时
剩下的我的时间
and the idiots took my house.
这些白痴占领了我的房子。
Which means those boobs
aren't around to bug me.
这意味着那些胸部
不会来打扰我。
Ooh, just what
I've been waiting for.
哦，只是什么
我一直在等待。
[ laughing hysterically]
[歇斯底里地大笑]
Iam going to relax,
if it kills me.
我要放松一下，
如果它杀了我。
Ah!
啊!
[ crowd screaming]
[人群尖叫]
Fire!
火！
Whoa, Squidward's house is
destroying the neighborhood.
哇哦，章鱼哥的家是
破坏邻居。
We got to turn
this thing off.
我们必须转身
这件事关了。
Nope, not it.
不，不是它。
[ toilet flushes]
Nope.
[马桶冲水]
不。
Nope.
没有。
That's not it, either.
也不是这样。
This Sunday relaxation
really hits the spot.
这周日放松一下
真的很到位。
Hmm, where to look?
嗯，去哪里看？
Hmm, this "off" button
seems suspicious.
嗯，这个“关闭”按钮
似乎很可疑。
We did it, Patrick!
我们做到了，帕特里克！
President Squidward...
章鱼哥总统...
No, no. Don't
say anything more.
不，不。不要
再说什么。
This was all my fault.
这都是我的错。
I was the one
who wanted to relax on Sunday.
我就是那个
谁想在周日放松一下。
Now, if you'll be so kind
as to leave,
现在，如果你能如此仁慈的话
至于离开，
so I can get ready
for work tomorrow.
这样我就可以做好准备
为了明天的工作。
Mr. President...
总统先生...
Shush.
嘘。
But we just
wanted to...
但我们只是
想要...
Get out of my house!
滚出我家！
Huh?
啊？
There
he is!
那里
他是！
Are you the owner
of this house?
你是业主吗
这所房子的？
Yes! Yes, I am!
是的！我是！
Then on behalf
那么代表
of the citizens
of Bikini Bottom,
公民的
比基尼泳裤，
I present you
with this summons
我向你介绍
有了这个传票
to pay for the destruction
of our town.
支付毁坏费用
我们镇的。
You'll be doing community
service every Sunday
你会做社区
每周日服务
for the rest of your life.
为你的余生。
Huh?
啊？
Squidward, you got
one of those, too?
章鱼哥，你有
也是其中之一吗？
This will be great--
这会很棒——
the three of us cleaning up
Bikini Bottom.
我们三个人打扫卫生
比基尼下装。
Well, see you next Sunday,
President Squidward.
嗯，下周日见
章鱼哥总统。
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
标题为
WGBH 媒体访问小组
访问.wgbh.org
标题为
WGBH 媒体访问小组
访问.wgbh.org